ski compensation for it is also possible at
ски компенсация за него ещ можно на
Soka I understand you are also handsome I am from the
Соку я понимаю ты тоже красавчик Я из
city of Khmelnitsk you are a girl
города Хмельницке вы девушка
from where I am from Crimea a From what city a
откуда Я из Крыма а Из какого города а
From what
Из какого
city
города
IT and what country is this Which country is this
ИТ а страна это какая страна
What kind of Russia do you
Какая Россия
do housework
занимаешся по
just Housewife housewife
дому просто Домохозяйка домохозяйка
got it This boar provides a little
понял Этот хряк немножко обеспечивает
you or
тебя или
not my boar how are you he you heard Yes he
нет мой хряк как ты он ты услышал Да он
is he he is
это
fighting hard and that is and when him if he then you will
зану воюет а то есть а когда его если он
be paid
то тебе выплатят
compensation No, of course he will be paid
компенсацию Нет ему мне конечно выплатят
compensation but
компенсацию но
you doubt it a lot like what what am
это ты очень много сомневаешься как бы о
I talking about  I want
чём О чём о чём я я я очень много хочу
to say a lot Well, it’s just that one girl from
сказать Ну просто мне одна девушка из
Simferopol told me that they didn’t pay compensation for her husband, the
Симферополя говорила что за мужа не
state deceived me. Is it true, or does it pay
государство Правда это или выплачивает
because Zakh Yaka, as it were, there is bgo
потому что зах Яка как бы это там бго
evil, it’s probably like this, well, they pay
зла наверное как бы это ну выплачивают
for the husband of the deceased or not. Are there payments from the
за мужа погибшего или нет Есть выплаты
state or not?  no, well, there is such a thing for a
государства или нет ну есть такое за
man who
мужчину кото который
is this And how much do they
это А сколько
pay?
платят
Well, 500 rubles rubles Yeah, what
Ну 500 руб руб Угу а что что на них
can
можно
you buy with them? What could you buy with these
купить что бы ты купила на эти ми
500? You can buy a lot. Well, for example,
500 много можно Что купить Ну например
what would you buy with these 1n
что бы ты купила на эти 1н
500 and apartments could  buy
500 и кварти могла бы купить
and
и
also
ещё
this is the
это
husband of the temple [ __ ] Sit next to you
муж висковый [__] Сить рядом
know the booze
знае буха
Rask with compensation for not
Раск с компенсация за не
moka just Naro
моку просто Наро
zafi I had a blast for
зафи Я отрывался за
Duma
Дума
Ducky just talked about people here
Даки просто про человеки рассказывал тут
pron stupidly Well, a lot of things can be
прон тупо Ну много что можно
bought in any
купить по-любому
role that
роли ту
rusty
ржа
letter nay Telegram right now the VN axis  and
пись най Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а
in the meantime, it’s even more and more respectful YouTube has taken
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or to your ban and even
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people at the moment I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams For this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, we need to write an operational link in Mali
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
and korisna
о вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and mi pon z you trimati
информация и ми пон з вами тримати
postiyny operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in togo chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
write
пиши